♪ I'll try to be a cat ♪ (According to the Literature Reading Group author monster monster if the fire novel work "today also want to be a cat" adaptation)
=Kucingku, Pacarku=
[Episode 5]
= Episode 5 =
(Two years ago)
(Dua tahun lalu)
Are you scared?
Takut tidak?
Or
Bagaimana kalau
Let's change to a cartoon.
Kita ganti kartun
I will be scared.
Aku takut?
Don't change it.
Tidak ganti.
This one.
Yang ini.
Are you sure?
Yakin?
I like to watch movies with the lights off.
Aku suka menonton film dengan mematikan lampu.
Just close it.
Tutup saja.
Who are you afraid of?
Siapa takut?
that
Kalau begitu
Here we go.
Mulai.
This movie is really good.
Film ini bagus sekali.
It's indeed the best story this year.
Memang drama terbaik tahun ini.
Aren't you scared?
Bukankah kamu tidak takut?
Finished
Gawat.
The movie was so boring that I nearly fell asleep.
Film ini membosankan. Aku sudah tertidur.
Really?
Benarkah?
There's a figure.
Ada bayangan orang.
Where is it?
Di mana?
Over there.
Di sebelah sana.
Why are you laughing?
Kamu tertawa apa?
You are still like a child.
Kamu masih sama seperti saat kecil
You're stubborn.
Suka keras kepala.
If you had told me earlier, we would have finished earlier.
Jika kamu mengatakannya lebih awal, kita tidak akan segera selesai.
I'm not scared.
Aku tidak takut.
Okay, I believe your silly sister.
Baik, aku percaya padamu, adik bodoh.
You're home alone today.
Hari ini kamu sendirian di rumah,
Don't be afraid.
Kamu jangan takut.
I'm leaving now.
Aku pergi dulu.
Why are you still here?
Kenapa belum pergi?
It's getting late outside.
Di luar sudah malam,
I suddenly thought of
Aku tiba-tiba teringat
There are several places in this movie today.
Hari ini film ini ada beberapa tempat
Not so good.
Tidak terlalu bagus.
You must have no idea.
Kamu pasti juga tidak tahu
I'll teach you.
Aku ajari kamu
Thank you so much, Miss Pei.
Terima kasih banyak pada Guru Pei.
Please come in.
Cepat masuk.
Don't mention it.
Jangan sungkan.
To show my gratitude,
Untuk berterima kasih,
Mr. Pei, you can sleep in the bed tonight.
Malam ini Guru Pei, Anda tidur di ranjang.
What about me?
Aku?
You can sleep on the couch.
Tidur di sofa saja.
Just right
Kebetulan sekali.
It's me.
Aku...
And a few acting problems.
Masih ada beberapa masalah akting.
I want to ask you.
Ingin bertanya pada Anda.
No animals were harmed during the filming.
(Tidak ada hewan yang terluka saat syuting film ini)
(The right to rebroadcast the play on the Internet belongs to me.) (Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.)
(Hak siar jaringan informasi serial kembali) [Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd.] Eksklusif untuk menikmati)